>> Brian Holt: 现在我们想为搜索参数编写一些测试。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now we wanna write
some tests for search params.
但我们在这里有点问题， iit's 搜索参数会发出 Ajax 电话。
But we have a bit of a problem here,
iIt's that search params makes Ajax calls.
你不想坐在你的测试中等待 Ajax 呼叫完成
And you don't wanna sit around in your
test waiting for Ajax calls to complete,
你也不想在每次测试时都锤打你的 API 对吧
nor do you wanna hammer your API
every time you run the tests, right?
那我们该怎么办
So what do we do about that?
我其实已经写了一个假的
Well one thing,
I actually have already written a mock for
这样我们就能用屁股了对吧
this, so we could use the mocks, right?
但我们不会这么做的
But we're not gonna do that.
实际上我们要给你写一个模拟的模拟自我
We're actually going to write a manual
mock ourselves just to show you
那是怎么运作的
how that works.
>> Brian Holt: 因此不在源中
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So inside of not the source
目录， >> Brian Holt: 在
directory,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Inside of
这里的顶级目录我要去做另一个文件夹
the top level directory here,
I'm gonna make another folder.
还有一个文件夹我们会打个电话
So another folder here and
we're gonna call
这个 __mocks__ ，有一个，可以吗 ?
this __mocks__, with an s, okay?
在 __mocks__ 中，我们将创建另一个文件夹
Inside of __mocks__,
we're gonna create another folder
称为 frontendmasters， >> Brian Holt:
called frontendmasters,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Which it is
代表它在前面的主人 /宠物
going to represent that it's
at frontendmasters/pet.
所以在前面的主人里我们要制作另一个叫宠物的文件
So inside of frontendmasters we
gonna make another file called pet.
所以这就很重要了，对吧 ?
So it is significant what it is called,
right?
如果我想嘲笑 Axios
If I wanted to mock Axios for an example,
我要在 __mocks__ 称为 Axios 的内部创建一个文件夹，对吗 ?
I would make a folder inside of
__mocks__ called Axios, right?
不是文件夹，而是文件。
Not a folder but a file.
>> Brian Holt: 因此这很重要，这叫做宠物。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
this is important that this is called pet.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，这将在节点内部运行。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
this is gonna be run inside of node.
因此，我可以使用导入 [ readFileSync ]
So I can use import [ readFileSync ]
从 "fs" 为节点核心库。
from 'fs' which is a node core library.
我要从 " 路径" 导入路径
I'm going to import path from 'path', and
我要从 " 反应测试库 " 中导入 [ act ] 。
I'm going to import [ act ]
from 'react-testing-library'.
因此，路径也来自节点本身。
So path again comes from
the node itself as well.
然后，行为来自 React 测试渲染器。
And then act comes from
the React test renderer.
它是如何在它被重新渲染的过程中跟踪的。
It's how it actually keeps track
of when it's supposed to rerender.
所以你要用这个动作，我们一会儿就知道了。
So you actually have to use this act
thing, we'll see that in just a second.
然后我们就会做些模拟数据
And then here we're just
gonna make some mock data.
所以我决定让他们以我最喜欢的名字命名
So const breeds equals, I decided to
make them named after my favorite
狗的家里人都是比丘尼族，比雄火种。
family of dog breeds which is
the Bichon group, Bichon Frise.
> > Brian Holt: 我们会制作其中的五个。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
we'll make five of these.
>> Brian Holt: 因此 Bichon Flise ，另一个是
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
Bichon Frise, another one is
a Bolognese， >> Brian Holt: And
a Bolognese,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
这是一个，让我们去做一个柯顿 - 德图勒
this is a, let's do a Coton de Tulear.
如果你没见过这品种的狗，它们很可爱，我甚至都做不到。
If you've not seen these breed of dogs,
they're adorable, I just can't even.
>> Brian Holt: 当然，我最喜欢的一个，因为那是我的狗，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Of course, my favorite one,
because it's what my dog is,
她是个哈瓦人
she's a Havanese.
我们把马尔泰塞也放在这里
And we'll put Multese in here as well.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，那是我们的一些很好的模拟数据。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
that's some good mock data for us.
然后我们会从 API中获取一些模拟数据。
And then we're gonna get
some mock data from an API.
所以我们要调用 cons daggos = JSON.parse (readFileSync)。
So we're gonna call cons daggos
= JSON.parse (readFileSync).
>> Brian Holt: 导入， readFileSync 从
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Import that,
readFileSync from
path.join dirname ，然后 res.json。
path.join dirname and then res.json.
>> Brian Holt: 然后放入 toString。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then put that toString.
>> Brian Holt: 这是一点节点魔术。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
this is a little bit of node magic.
如果你不太了解这一点，那就好。
If you don't really understand
it that much, that's okay.
这只是确保您从正确的目录获取文件，对吗 ?
This is just making sure that you get
the file from the right directory, right?
这将确保在同一目录中，我们将
So this is going to make sure that inside
of the same directory, we're gonna
有一个叫 res.json 的东西，它将从 res.json中读出来。
have something called res.json and
it's going to be reading from res.json.
所以我要你做的，我为你做了这个 res.json 文件。
So what I want you to do,
I've made this res.json file for you.
所以来完成--简介 - 反应 - v5，让我们把它转至测试分支。
So coming to complete-intro-to-react-v5,
let's hop over to the testing branch.
那就跳吧在那创造
So hop on that, create there.
然后在这个里面，里面有一个 res.json 文件。
And then inside of this, inside of mocks,
there's this res.json file.
让我们点击这个
Let's click on that.
> > Brian Holt: 我想我有一个， yep.
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I think I have a, yep.
我也有这方面的联系。
I also have a link to this as well.
所以如果你进了完整的反反应 - v5
So if you go into
the complete-intro-to-react-v5,
去测试最后一个在这下面的
go down to testing,
the last one underneath this one here,
我们有这个地方说要去复印和贴这个夹具
we have this part where it says go and
copy and paste this fixture.
所以就这样了对吧
So it's this, right?
所以就复制全部
So just copy all.
>> Brian Holt: 在同一目录中创建新文件并保存该文件，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Make a new file here in
the same directory and save it called,
前面有个叫雷斯.json的人
inside of frontendmasters called res.json.
>> Brian Holt: 正如你所看到的，它有 1100 行的 API 响应，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And as you can see, it's
1,100 lines of API response stuff, right?
>> Brian Holt: 现在，此处的狗只代表此文件。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now,
doggos here will represent this file.
这条线就这么简单就能抓住那个文件
That's all that this line does,
is it just goes and grabs that file and
把它变成一个物体好吗
parses it into an object, okay?
> > Brian Holt: 现在我们需要做的是在这里说几件事。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now what we need to do is
we're gonna say a couple of things here.
我们会说出口 ANIMALS = ['dog'，
We're gonna say export ANIMALS = ['dog',
" 猫咪 " " 鸟人 "
'cat', 'bird'].
你可以把更多的人放在这里
You can put more of them in here but for
现在我们只把它做个简单的动物名单
now we'll just make this
a short list of animals.
出口 const ， export const.
Export const rather, export const.
导出 const _reeds = repds。
Export const _breeds = breeds.
我在此强调，这只是为了进行测试。
I do underscore here just to signify
this is only meant to be for testing.
这不是一般消费的意思。
It's not meant for general consumption.
出口常量_do犬
And export const _dogs
= 狗头动物。
= doggos.animals.
所以我们测试夹具的内部
So inside of our testing fixtures,
we'll test for
这些都是为了确保他们的匹配对吧
these to make sure that they match up,
right?
> > Brian Holt: 接下来，我们会制作一个非常快速的模拟库。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then here, we're just
gonna make a really quick mock library.
所以 const mock = 一个对象，我们要测试品种。
So const mock = an object,
and we're gonna test breeds.
我们要做个 jest.fn
And we're gonna make this a jest.fn.
> > Brian Holt: 这称为间谍功能，稍后您将检查
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This is called a spy
function which you're gonna check later to
请确保已调用此函数。
make sure this function has been called.
所以我们要给它一个实施细节
And so we're gonna give it
an implementation detail where it's just
会说每当有人打电话给 jest.fn 的时候
gonna say, whenever someone calls jest.fn,
or calls rather mock.breeds,
调用此函数，然后返回， >> Brian Holt: 一个对象
call this function and then return,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: An object
然后再回电对吧
with a then callback, right?
我答应过的对吧
It's promised like, right?
这将是一个回调， >> Brian Holt: 那就是所谓的行为。
And this is gonna be a callback,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: That then calls act.
这是另一个函数
That is another function that
返回带有 doggos的回调。
returns callback with doggos.
所以我意识到这有点复杂但
So I recognize that this is
a little convoluted here, but
让我们先走一步好吗
let's just kinda step through it, okay?
所以我们正在建立一个模拟的宠物图书馆，对吧 ?
So we're creating a mock library of pet,
right?
所以我们一直在叫我们的宠物 API 客户
So we've been calling our pet API
client all over the place and
我们正在制造一个像它一样的物体对吧
we're creating an object
that looks like it, right?
看起来像是它的样子
Looks and acts like it.
它有一个品种的功能，对吧 ?
It has a breeds function, right?
所以我们在制造一种间谍功能，我们可以说，后来，
So we're making breeds a spy function that
we can say, later, make sure this was
打电话，确定是用这些东西来的，等等。
called, make sure it was called with
these things, so on and so forth.
它将会运行这个功能
It's going to run this
function which is then
能返回一个类似诺言的东西对吧
going to return a promise-like object,
right?
所以当我说承诺的时候，它是一个有功能的物体，对吧 ?
So when I say promise-like, it's an object
that has a then function on it, right?
所以这看起来像在这里做出的承诺。
So this looks and
acts like a promise right here.
这为自己提供了功能，对吗 ?
This has provided itself
with the function, right?
我们得说这件事让我们做出反应
And we have to call this act
thing to let react know like,
我更新了一些东西，去做些什么，对吧 ?
I updated something,
go do something with that, right?
>> Brian Holt: 所以有点复杂，但这就是你的方式。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
a little convoluted but this is how you.
这也是我不喜欢测试 UI 代码的原因
This is again probably why I don't
like testing UI code is cuz you kinda
得把细节弄明白
have to get into the details with it.
我们会用动物做同样的事
We're gonna do the same
thing with animals.
>> Brian Holt: 它将是另一 jest.fn或 jest.fn。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's gonna be
another jest.fn, or jest.fn.
>> Brian Holt: 将返回一个对象，该对象具有以下功能 :
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And it's going to return
an object with the then function which is
在一个叫回叫的回叫上
going to take in a callback which is
then going to return an act which
就会用狗带来称呼回调
is then going to call
the callback with doggos.
这个不叫狗儿这只叫狗
Yeah, this one doesn't call doggos,
this one calls breeds.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 对不起，第 24 行，确定那是品种
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So sorry, line 24 there,
make sure that that's breeds and
这条狗的狗
this one's doggos.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，现在有两个功能。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
now you have two functions.
这只会带来繁殖
This one returns breeds eventually,
是我们在这里嘲笑的这个对吧
which is this one that we mocked up here,
this one, right?
然后我们又有了一条狗
And then we have one that returns doggos.
还有一件事第 24 行
And, one more thing, line 24.
我们需要这个对象是一种繁殖的对象 :
We need this to be an object which
is breeds: breeds, like that, or
你可以把它称为 " 品种 " 就像这样
you can just call it breeds, like this,
因为 API的响应必须相同，否则代码将失败。
because the API's response has to look
identical or else the code's gonna fail.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，我保证
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, that's it, I promise.
所以现在在下面我们可以说出口默认模型
[LAUGH] So now at the bottom here
we can say export default mock,
但最酷的是我们最棒的时候如果它说我有个假的
but what's cool is anytime inside of
our jest if it says, I have a mock for
这个，只要有人在 jest 里面进口前面的主人/宠物，
this, anytime that someone imports
frontendmasters/pet inside of jest,
我要用这个代替真正的图书馆吧
I'm gonna use this instead
of the real library, right?
所以现在我控制了这个，这很不错。
So now I have control over this,
which is good.
>> Brian Holt: 现在您可能在想， jest 未定义。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now you might be wondering,
jest is not defined.
这将是一个由 jest 提供给我们的全球性变量。
This is gonna be a global
variable provided to us by jest.
如果他们进入我们的 eslint.json 文件
And we can make eslint to be okay with
that if they go into our eslint.json file
说，哎， env，我们也有 jest。
and say, hey, env, we also have jest.
说真的然后现在一切都好了
And just say true, and
then now everything's happy.